SERJ QAZI FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Linkedin | GitHub | Twitter | Portfolio

226-501-5420



sirajum.qazi@gmail.com



Guelph, Ontario

PROFILE

I am a Front-End Developer with a passion for making impactful web applications that are accessible and responsive, using my skills in React, JavaScript, HTML & SASS. My extensive experience in customer service and strong background in sales allows me to collaborate and make meaningful connections with others.

SOFT SKILLS

- · Spirited team player & collaborator
- · Coaching & mentoring others
- Tactfulness

SKILLS

- React (Hooks & Classes)
- JavaScript ES6+
- HTML5, CSS3, SASS
- Responsive Design
- RESTful APIs & Firebase
- Git & GitHub collaboration
- Version control
- Paired programming in teams
- Project scope management

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology, Ontario

2020 - 2021 - FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPMENT

- Web Development Bootcamp
- Intro to JavaScript (jQuery)
- Intro to Web Development

Oliver's Learning, Alberta

2015 - 2016 - HLLQP - FINANCIAL BROKER LICENSE

- Life Insurance
- Investment
- Wealth Management

PROJECT

Robo Trivia - React App

< a />

- Solo or Multiplayer trivia game
- API to generate questions & multiple choice answers, assigns avatars to usernames
- Firebase to keep user data and score

Find My Beer - React App

< a />

- A way to find all the breweries in your state
- API to generate a list of breweries
- Font of card shows name and address
- · Back of card shows brewery type, contact info and website
- Fully responsive and mobile compatible

Recipe Lookup - Javascript

< a />

- Vanilla JavaScript combined with SASS
- A simple yet elegant way to look up a recipe for anything you want to cook
- Pick your ingredients to receive recipes

EXPERIENCE

Linamar, Guelph Ontario

2017 - 2020

- Troubleshoot and setup CNC lathes to ensure safe operation at production startup
- Trained new employees to operate CNC lathes safely & effectively to maintain production quality and target

Sherwood Ford, Edmonton, Alberta

2015 - 2017

- Managed the internet sales team by recruiting, scheduling & assisting team mates to meet our sales targets
- Contacted new & existing customers to promote new sales events

HOBBIES

Twitch streaming | Graphic design | Photography